父亲要我们继续他的遗志
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off:
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 这是家族事业
Saving people, hunting things, the family business.
我做了些恶梦 有时候这些梦成真了
I have these nightmares, and sometimes they come true.
又做梦了？
Come again?
我梦到过在杰西卡死前的景象
I dreamt about Jessica's death before it happened.
一个影像 以恶梦的形式出现
A vision. It started as nightmares.
后来就算醒着 他也会有这样的影像
It started happening while he was awake.
离那魔鬼越近 那些影像更清晰
The closer I get to the demon, the stronger the visions get.
那魔鬼说 他已经为我和其他人规划好了一切
The demon, he said he had plans for me and children like me.
- 你知道他是什么意思？- 我不知道
- You have any idea what he meant? - No, I don't.
马克斯 你拥有的能力 是不是在六七个月前开始的？
Max, your abilities, they started six, seven months ago?
- 你怎么知道？- 我也是在那个时候拥有特殊能力的
- How'd you know that? - That's when mine started.
是同一个魔鬼杀死了我们的母亲 我们是被他选中的
The same thing killed our mothers. And you and I are chosen.
- 选中做什么 - 我不知道
- For what? - I don't know.
我不知道是什么原因 大概因为我们有相似之处吧？
The thing I don't get is why, man. I guess because we're so alike?
马克斯和你没有相似之处 萨姆 马克斯是个怪物
He is nothing like you. He is a monster.
他已经杀了二个人了 现在正要杀第三个人
He's already killed two people, now he's gunning for a third.
他对你说了什么？
Did he say anything to you?
没有 没什么
No. Nothing.
你好 医生
Hey, doc.
哈喽？是的
Hello? Yeah.
好的
All right.
- 下午好丹尼斯 - 嘿 医生
- Afternoon, Dennis. - Hey, doc.
- 我想看看枪 - 好的 医生
- I'd like to look at a gun. - Yeah, right, doc.
你认真的？
Seriously?
那把
That one.
好
Okay.
这是土耳其猎枪 12口径 手动上膛
That's a turkey hunter. Twelve gauge, pump action.
要我说 这比土耳其造的好多了
Don't leave enough turkey behind, you ask me.
什么 嗯 用的是什么子弹？
What sort of shells does it use?
这个
Right here.
这个周末我把打算带孩子去小屋 如果你 嗯…
I'm taking the boys up to the cabin this weekend, if you're, uh…
我意思是如果你对打猎感兴趣的话
I mean, if you think you might like to take up the sport.
谢谢 我没兴趣 枪会让我变得紧张 而且总是这样
Thanks, but no. You know guns make me nervous, always have.
- 是这样装是吗？- 哇噢 医生 不不
- This one goes in here, right? - Whoa, doc, no, no.
你不能在室里上膛 这是不合法的
You can't load on the premises. It's illegal.
- 没事的丹尼斯 - 不不
- It's okay, Dennis. - No, no
没事的丹尼斯 一切都会…
It's okay, Dennis. It's all gonna be…
- … 没事 - 医生
- …okay. - Doc!
不不 没事
No. No, it's okay.
没事 一切都会… 没事的
It's okay. It's all gonna be okay.
萨姆 快点 把拉链拉上 让我们… 上路
Sam, come on, zip it up. Let's hit the road.
怎么了？
What?
[邪恶力量 第2季第5集]
我不知道 为什么不冷静下来想想这事？
I don't know, man. Why don't we just chill out, think about this?
有什么好想的？
What's there to think about?
只是不知道 去罗德豪斯是不是个好主意
Don't know if going to the Roadhouse is smart.
迪恩 又一个前兆 没错的
It's another premonition. I know it.
- 这一定会发生的 阿什会告诉我们地点 - 是 但是
- This will happen. Ash can tell us where. - Yeah, but
而且这或许和那个魔鬼有关
Could have a connection with the demon.
- 我的影像一直很准的 - 这就是我要说的
- My visions always do. - That's my point.
那里也许有猎捕者了 我不知道…
There will be hunters. Don't know if announcing…
我们到那儿 说你是个什么超能力的
that you're some supernatural freak with a demonic connection…
和魔鬼有联系的怪胎会是什么好事
is the best thing, okay?
那现在我是怪胎喽？
So I'm a freak now?
你一直都是
You've always been a freak.
妈的 小姐 这是我的房租钱
Damn, little lady, that was my room money.
我想你今晚要在车里睡一晚了
I guess you're taking a truck nap tonight.
在你把钱放进去前 最好看看最高分记录是谁
Ought to check the high scores before you put your money down.
快点走吧 Ed
Went and got yourself hustled, Ed.
- 走的不太远 是吧？- 是的 好像是的 过的怎么样 乔？
- Just can't stay away, huh? - Yeah, looks like. How you doing, Jo?
- 阿什在哪？- 在后屋
- Where's Ash? - In his backroom.
- 很好 - 我过得很好
- Great. - And I'm fine.
抱歉他有点急
Sorry, he's-We're kind of on a bit of a timetable.
阿什？
Mm-hm.
夏普斯维尔镇的悲剧 好像又要重现了…
Ash.
嘿 阿什？
Hey, Ash.
嘿 坏蛋博士？
Hey, Dr. Badass.
萨姆 迪恩 萨姆和迪恩
Sam. Dean. Sam and Dean.
嘿 阿什
Hey, Ash. Um…
嗯 我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
妈的 看来要穿上裤子了
Oh, hell, then. Guess I need my pants.
我找到和这相符的了 是布卢里奇汽车站的标志
I got a match. It's the logo for the Blue Ridge Bus Lines.
- 在俄克拉何马州的格思里 - 那好 帮忙找一下在格思里
- Guthrie, Oklahoma. - Okay, do me a favor.
有没有魔鬼的踪迹 或和其有关的
Check Guthrie for any demonic signs or omens or anything like that.
你认为魔鬼在那里？
You think the demon's there?
- 是的 有这可能 - 为什么这么想？
- Yeah, maybe. - Why would you think that?
查查 好吗？
Just check it, all right?
没有 朋友 什么也没有 没有魔鬼踪迹
No, sir, nothing. No demon.
那好 再帮我查下别的
All right, try something else for me.
查一下格思里那的房屋起火事件 发生在1983年的
Search Guthrie for a house fire. It would be 1983.
火灾是从育婴室开始的
Fire's origin would be a baby's nursery…
时间是在孩子六个月的生日
night of the kid's 6-month birthday.
好 现在觉得的有点奇怪 朋友
Okay, now, that is just weird, man.
我他妈的为什么要找这些？
Why the hell would I be looking for that?
- 因为查了这东西归你了 - 给我十五分钟
- Because there's a PBR in it for you. - Give me 15 minutes.
- 查到什么？- R。-E。-O。-的Speedwagon？
- What? - REO Speedwagon?
就是这个R。-E。-O 凯文·克罗宁是用心在唱这首歌
Damn right, REO. Kevin Cronin sings it from the heart.
他是用头发在唱的 这就是不同之处
He sings it from the hair. There's a difference.
你们要阿什查的的那个案子
That profile you've got Ash looking for.
你妈也是这样死的 是吗？死在萨姆育婴室里的火中？
Your mom died the same way, didn't she? A fire in Sam's nursery?
乔 这是我们自家事
Jo, it's kind of a family thing.
- 我可以帮助你们 - 我知道你能帮上忙
- I could help. - I'm sure you could.
但我们想自己处理这事
But we gotta handle this one ourselves.
而且 如果我把你拖下水 你妈会杀了我
Besides, if I ran off with you, your mother might kill me.
- 你怕我妈？- 我是这么认为的
- You're afraid of my mother? - I think so.
- 我们找到相符的了 我们得走了 - 好了 乔 待会儿再见
- We have a match. We gotta go. - All right, Jo. See you later.
∮ 即使在我徘徊的时候 ∮
∮ And even as I wander. ∮
∮ 我一直在看你 ∮
∮ I'm keeping you in sight. ∮
∮ 你是橱窗里的蜡烛 ∮
∮ You're a candle in the window. ∮
∮ 在寒冷黑暗的冬夜 ∮
∮ On a cold, dark winter's night. ∮
∮ 我越来越近了 比我想象的要近 我可能… ∮
∮ And I'm getting closer.Than I ever thought.I might… ∮
你唱上瘾了是吧？
You're kidding, right?
在别处听到这首歌 就在脑中挥之不去了
Heard it somewhere, can't get it out of my head.
我也不知道为什么 有什么发现？
I don't know, man. What do you got?
安得烈·加拉赫 1983年出生 和我一样
Andrew Gallagher. Born in '83, like me.
育婴室火灾烧死了她的母亲 当时他也只有六个月大
Lost his mother in a nursery fire exactly six months later
这一点也和我一样
also like me.
你认为那魔鬼杀死了他的母亲？
You think the demon killed his mom?
- 貌似如此 - 你知道怎么样找到这个人？
- Looks like it. - How did you know to look?
如果不是和那魔鬼有关 我为什么会有那些前兆
If premonitions aren't about the demon
前兆的内容都是关于魔鬼选定的孩子
they're about the kids the demon visited.
就像马克斯 米勒 还记得他吗？
Like Max Miller, remember him?
当然 但马克斯 米勒是个彻底的疯子
Yes.But Max Miller was a pasty little psycho.
问题是他杀了人
He was killing people
而且那些影像我都预见到了
and I was having the same type of visions about him.
现在这一切又重现了 而且是在加拉赫那个人身上
It could be happening again with this Gallagher.
- 我们如何能找到他？- 我不知道
- How do we find him? - Don't know.
没有当前住址 没有就职资料
No current address, no current employment.
欠支票钱 电话费 信用卡费 还有其它一些费用
Still owes money on all his bills. Phone, credit, utilities.
- 社工处呢？- 系统里也查不到
- Collection-agency flags? - None in the system.
- 他们就让他到处流荡 - 好像是这样
- They just let him take a walk? - Seems like it.
从W- 2里得到了他一年前工作的地址
There's a work address from his last W2, about a year ago.
那我们就从那里开始
We'll start there.
你从安迪那里问不到什么的 不好意思 他们从没问到过
You won't get anything out of Andy, guys. I'm sorry, but they never do.
- 「他们」？- 你们是收帐的 是吗？
- They? - You're debt collectors, right?
有一次他们过来
Once in a while, they come by.
我不知道安迪对他们说了什么 但他们就再也没有来过
I don't know what Andy says to them, but they never come back.
事实上 我们代表他的姨祖母丽塔的律师
Actually, we're lawyers, representing his Great-aunt Lita.
她过世了 愿她安息 但她留了点房产给安迪
She passed, God rest her soul, but left Andy a sizable estate.
是吗 那你是他的朋友吗？
Yeah. So are you a friend of his?
我以前是 但最近我没见到过他
I used to be, yeah. I don't see much of Andy anymore.
安迪？安迪很棒 朋友
Andy? Andy kicks ass, man.
- 是吗？- 是的
- Is that right? - Yes.
安迪什么事都办得到
Andy can get you into anything.
有次甚至带我去了Aerosmith乐团的后台
He got me backstage at Aerosmith once.
那里真是美极了 伙计
It was beautiful, bro.
韦伯 是不是还有一两张桌子没擦？
Uh-huh. How about busing a table or two, Webber?
好吧 你说了算 老板
Yeah. You bet, boss.
听着 如果你们想找到他 到奥查德街去找找
Look, if you wanna find him, try Orchard Street.
只要去找一辆在车身喷有 野蛮女王图案的货车就行了
Look for a van with a barbarian queen painted on the side.
野蛮女王
Barbarian queen.
那车很显眼 不会错过的
She's riding a polar bear. It's kind of hard to miss.
抱歉 我已经开始喜欢那位朋友了 这货车真是赞
I'm sorry, I'm starting to like this dude. That van is sweet.
- 怎么回事？- 没事
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
萨姆 你看上去像吃了个酸柠檬
You look like you're sucking a lemon. What's going on?
这是安得烈·加拉赫 他是第二个像我一样的人
Andrew Gallagher. He's the second guy like this we've found.
魔鬼在他们还是孩子的时候去过 现在他们正在杀人
Demon came when they were kids, now they kill people.
我们不了解安得烈·加拉赫的情况 他可能是无辜的
We don't know what Andrew is. Could be innocent.
- 我的前兆从没有错过 - 你是什么意思？
- My visions haven't been wrong yet. - What's your point?
- 我的意思是我和他们一样 - 不 你和他们不同
- My point is I'm one of them. - No, you're not.
迪恩 那魔鬼说已经给我们 这些孩子规划好了一切
The demon said he had plans for me and children like me.
- 是吗？- 也许这只是他的计划
- Yeah? - Yeah, maybe this is his plan.
也许我们是一群有超能力的怪胎
Maybe we're all a bunch of psychic freaks.
也许我们都会成为…
Maybe we're all supposed to be
- 凶手？- 是吗
- What, killers? - Yeah.
所以那魔鬼想你来这用你的意念杀人？
The demon wants you out there killing with your minds, is that it?
饶了我吧 你不是杀人犯 萨姆
Give me a break. You're not a murderer, Sam.
- 你没有这个胆量去杀人 - 没有吗？
- You don't have it in your bones. - No?
上次我记得我有杀过
Last I checked, I kill all kinds of things.
那是他自找的 那就是区别
But those things were asking for it. There's a difference.
他现身了
Got him.
是他 那个老男人 就是他开的枪
That's him. That older guy. That's him. He's the shooter.
那好 你跟着他 我盯着安迪
Well, you keep on him. I'll stick with Andy. Go.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey, hey.
- 这车不错 - 是的 谢谢
- This is a cherry ride. - Yeah, thanks.
朋友 我得说 67年的高角羚是最棒的
Manual '67. Impala's best year, if you ask me.
这真是经典啊
This is a serious classic.
你知道吗 我刚重装过
Yeah. Well, you know, I just rebuilt her.
- 我可不想让它报废了 - 说的对
- Can't let a car like this one go. - Damn straight.
嘿 我能不能开一下？
Hey, can I have it?
- 当然 伙计 - 好人
- Sure, man. - All right. Sweet.
进去吧
Hop right in there.
- 你开吧 - 很好
- There you go. - That is nice.
- 放轻松 - 好的
- Take it easy. - All right.
哈喽？是我
Hello? Yeah.
哈喽 是我
Hello? Yeah. All right.
- 迪恩 安迪在开高角羚 - 我知道啊
Andy's got the Impala. - I know.
他让我借他开开 我就让他开了
He just sort of asked me for it and I let him take it.
- 你什么？- 他控制了我
- You what? - He full on Obi Wan'd me.
我的意识被他控制了
It's mind control, man.
我阻止他进枪枝店
I kept him out of the gun store.
我还以为他会没事
Thought he was okay.
我想他能逃过这一关的 至少…
I thought he was past it, at least
我应该跟紧点
I should've stayed with him.
你好吗 朋友？
Andy. What's up, dog?
安迪 你在这干什么？
Andy. What are you doing here?
詹宁斯医生 他死了
Dr. Jennings, he's dead.
喔 不 真是抱歉
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
我不知道 我 我…
I don't know.
我只是很伤心 我想来见你
I was upset and I wanted to see you.
很高兴你来见我
Well, I'm glad you did.
我 嗯…
I, um…
我很想你
I missed you.
你知道吗？今天早上有人到这来找你
You know what? Some guys were here this morning, looking for you.
什么人？
What guys?
感谢上帝
Thank God.
对不起亲爱的 我不会再离开你了
I'm sorry, baby. I'll never leave you again.
至少他把车钥匙留下了
At least he left the keys in it.
是的 这朋友真的不错
Yeah. Real Samaritan, this guy.
他好像不是凭空就能控制别人
He can't work his mojo by twitching his nose.
好像要通过声音来操纵
He's gotta use verbal commands.
那医生走到车前时正在听电话
Doctor had just gotten off his cell phone when he stepped in front of that bus.
肯定是安迪打电话给他 或是其它什么的
Andy must have called or something.
我不知道 也许…
I don't know, maybe…
- 你说什么？- 我只是不确定他是不是我们要找的人
- Beg your pardon? - I don't know if he's our guy.
在他没有下车前你也认定他有罪了
You had O.J. convicted before he got out of his Bronco
可现在你却对此表示怀疑了？
and you doubt this?
他不像是冷血杀手那型 就是这意思
He doesn't seem like the stone cold killer type, that's all.
而且我只是说他心虚了
And O.J. was guilty.
那我们要怎么让他就犯
Either way, how are we gonna track this guy down?
那不是问题
Not a problem.
真是个惹人注意的车子
Not exactly an inconspicuous ride.
让我们看看
Let's have a look.
喔 拜托
Oh, come on.
这是… 这真是壮观 真的是壮观
This is magnificent, that's what this is.
不像是连环杀手的后车箱
Not exactly a serial killer's lair, though.
墙上没有小丑
There's no clown paintings on the walls
也没有剪过的受害者的照片上
or scissors stuck in victims' photos.
我喜欢这老虎
Like the tiger.
黑格尔？康德？都是蛮深奥的小说
Hegel, Kant, Wittgenstein. That's some pretty heavy reading, Dean.
是的 嗯… 电影《白鲸》里的水烟枪
Yeah, and, uh, ahem, Moby Dick's bong.
你知道吗 总有一天我会坐在那
You know, one day, I'd love to just sit down…
吃着不需要在小超市里 用微波炉加热的食品
and eat something I didn't have to microwave at a mini mart.
我不知道杀人的动机是什么 那个医生的背景很清白
What I don't get is the motive. I mean, the doctor was squeaky clean.
- 为什么安迪要干掉他？- 如果是安迪干的话
- Why would Andy waste him? - If it is Andy.
- 哥们 够了 - 为什么啊？
- Dude, enough. - What?
如果那医生在走到车前时 心智是被人控制的
The doctor was mind controlled in front of a bus.
而安迪正好能控制人的心智 你自己想想吧
Andy happens to have the power of mind control. You do the math.
- 我不认为是那家伙做的 - 你到底是怎么想的？
- I don't think he's got it in him. - How would you know?
- 为什么要处处维护他？- 因为你错了
- Why are you defending him? - You're not right.
- 关于安迪吗？- 嘿 你们以为我没看见你们吗？
- About Andy? - Hey. You think I haven't seen you two?
为什么跟踪我？
Why are you following me?
我们是律师 你的一个亲戚…
Well, we're lawyers. A relative of yours has passed
说实话
Tell the truth.
- 事实是… - 我们猎杀魔鬼
- That's what I'm…We hunt demons.
- 什么？- 迪恩
- What? - Dean.
魔鬼和鬼魂 一些你噩梦中的怪物
Demons, spirits. Things your worst nightmares wouldn't touch.
- 萨姆是我的弟弟 - 迪恩 闭嘴
- Sam here is my brother. - Shut up.
我在努力 他和你一样神经
I'm trying. He's psychic, like you.
不全像你 他认为你是杀人犯
Not really like you. He thinks you're a murderer.
他担心会变成你那样 因为你们都经历过一些恐怖的事情
He's afraid he'll be one, because you're all part of something terrible.
我希望他是错的 但是现在我开始害怕他也许说对了
I hope he's wrong, but I'm starting to get scared he might be right.
好吧 知道吗？
Okay, you know what?
离我远点
Just leave me alone.
- 好 - 好吗？
- Okay. - All right?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
听着 我 我说过了 离我远点
Look, I said leave me alone.
离开这里
Get out of here.
一直开不要停
Just start driving and never stop.
- 看起来对我没用 安迪 - 什么？
- Doesn't seem to work on me, Andy. - What?
你是不是可以让人们做事？控制他们的思想
You can make people do things. You can tell them what to think.
那是不可能的
Look, that's crazy.
那是一年前开始的 对吧？在你22岁后
It all started about a year ago, didn't it? After you turned 22.
开始只是一点点 渐渐地你就能控制好了
Little stuff, then you got better at control.
- 你怎么知道的？- 因为我和你一样 安迪
- How do you know all this? - Same thing happened to me.
我的妈妈也死在一场大火里 我也有超能力
My mom died in a fire too. I have abilities too.
你瞧 我们是联系在一起的 你和我
We're connected, you and me.
快点… 快点离开这里
Just get out of here.
为什么要让那个医生去撞公车？
Why'd you tell the doctor to walk in front of a bus?
什么？
What?
- 为什么要杀了他？- 我没有
- Why did you kill him? - I didn't.
嗨？
Hello?
是的 我可以做到
Sure. I can do that.
嘿
Hey!
- 女士 你在干什么呢？ - 没事的
- What are you doing? - It's okay.
女士 不 不要
Lady, no. No!
萨姆？是什么？
Sam. What is it?
不是我干的
Look, I didn't do anything to him.
- 一个女人活生生地自焚了 - 还看到什么？
- A woman burning alive. - What else did you get?
加油站 有一个女人将要自杀
A gas station. A woman is gonna kill herself.
- 他说「将」是什么意思？- 闭嘴
- What's he mean, "going to"? What's? - Shut up.
- 她是通过手机被控制的 - 什么时候？
- She gets triggered by a call on her cell. - When?
我不知道 只要我们看着这个混蛋 他就不能伤害她了
I don't know. As long as we keep our eyes on him, he can't hurt her.
- 我什么人也没伤害 - 是的 还没有呢
- I didn't hurt anybody. - Yeah, not yet.
快去
Go.
不 你别动 你得和我在一起
No, not you. You're staying here with me.
嘿 是我 她死了 烧死的 和你说的一样
Hey, it's me. She's dead. Burned up, just like you said.
- 什么时候？- 我赶到的几分钟前
- When? - Minutes before I got here.
焦味还没散开呢
Smell hasn't even cleared.
你看到的影像是怎么回事？根本不是前兆
What's with your visions? This wasn't a head start.
我控制不了 也不知道是怎么回事
I can't control them. I don't know what's going on.
当这事发生时安迪和你在一起
You were with Andy when this went down.
所以不是他干的 一定另有其人
It can't be him. It's gotta be somebody else.
- 没道理啊 - 那会是什么？
- That doesn't make any sense. - What else is new?
我会到处看看有什么其它线索
I'll dig around here, see what else I can find.
你能看看人们死前的前兆？
You get? You see premonitions of people about to die?
不可能吧
That's impossible.
很多人都和你说一样的话
A lot of people would say the same thing about what you do.
- 死亡景象？- 是的
- Death visions? - Yeah.
哥们 那真逊 当我能控制心智时
Dude, that sucks. I mean, like, when I got my mind thing?
那就像是种天赋 就像是中了头奖
It was like a gift, you know? It was like I won the lotto.
但你却还住在货车里
You still live in a van.
我不懂了 你什么都可以得到啊
I don't get it. I mean, you could have anything you ever wanted.
是的 但我 我已经知足了
I got everything I need.
那么你真不是杀手 呃？
So you're really not a killer, huh?
这是我一直想说的
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
那很好
That's good.
那意味着我们都有希望了
Means there's hope for both of us.
受害者的名字是 霍莉·贝克特 41岁 单身
Victim's name was Holly Beckett, 41, single.
- 她是谁？- 从没听过
- Who is she? - Never heard of her.
回来的时候打过电话给阿什 他查到了一点东西
Called Ash on the way here. He came up with something.
很显然霍莉·贝克特 在1983年18岁的时候就生过孩子
Apparently Holly Beckett gave birth when she was 18 years old in 1983.
和你的生辰一样 安迪
Same day you were born, Andy.
安迪 你是被领养的？
Andy, were you adopted?
- 是的 - 你是？
- Well, yeah. - You were?
- 但你没提过？- 没必要说啊
- And you neglected to mention that? - Never really came up.
我是说 我根本不认识我的亲生父母
I mean, I never knew my birth parents.
就像你说的 我的养母在我还是婴儿时就死了
And like you said, my adopted mom died when I was a baby.
你认为这个叫霍莉的女人 会不会真是…
Do you think this Holly woman could actually be my?
我不知道 试过去找出生证明
I don't know. Tried to get the birth records.
但是它们被锁在郡政府里
But they're hard copy only, sealed in the county office.
那就闯进去
Well, screw that.
也许不该让你们在这里
I probably shouldn't have let you kids in here.
不 不会有事的
No, it'll all be fine.
好吗？去买杯咖啡喝喝吧 好吗？
All right, just go get a cup of coffee. All right?
我们不是你需要看住的小孩子
And these aren't the droids you're looking for.
- 真棒 - 我找到了
- Awesome. - Got it.
- 是吗？是的
Yeah? - Yeah.
安迪 那是真的 霍莉·贝克特就是你的亲生母亲
Andy, it's true. Holly Beckett was your birth mother.
谁有止痛药吗？
Does anyone have a Vicodin?
詹宁斯医生也是她的医生 我是说 是他安排的领养
Dr. Jennings was her doctor too. I mean, he oversaw the adoption.
- 你和他们都有关联 - 是的 但我没杀他们
- You have a solid connection to them. - But I didn't kill them.
- 我们相信你
We believe you.
- 是的 - 但是 呃 谁干的？
- Yeah. - But who did?
我想我猜到了
I think I got a pretty good guess.
霍莉·贝克特生的是双胞胎
Holly Beckett gave birth to twins.
我有个邪恶的孪生兄弟
I have an evil twin.
霍莉把你和你兄弟送去领养机构
Holly put you and your brother up for adoption.
你被加拉赫家领养了
And you went to the Gallagher family, obviously.
而你的兄弟被州北的威姆斯家领养了
And your brother went to the Weems family from upstate.
安迪 你还好吗？在听吗？
Hey, Andy, how you doing? Still with us?
- 嗯… 我兄弟的名字是什么？- 这里 呃
- What was my brother's name? - Here. Um…
安塞姆·威姆斯？
Anson Weems.
这儿有他在这里的地址
He's got a local address.
- 他住在这里？- 让我们看看他吧
- He lives here? - About to get a look at him.
马上就能从交通部拿到他的照片了
There's a picture coming over from the DMV right now.
我讨厌被吓的感觉
Hate to kick you while you're freaked.
看看这个
Take a look at that.
- 嘿 特雷斯？- 什么事？
- Hey, Trace. - Yeah?
你和安迪 你们是不是在一起过？
You and Andy, you guys went together for a while, didn't you?
- 是的 韦伯 怎么了？- 没什么 只是想知道
- Yeah, Webber, why? - I don't know, I was just wondering.
我只是想知道这些天你对他的感觉
I was wondering how you felt about him these days.
我看到你们在一起 感觉你们之间还有感情的
I've seen you guys together. It seems like there's still something there.
你们想过… 要… 认真过吗？
Were you guys ever, like, serious?
- 嗯… 没有 - 得了 特雷斯
- Um, no. - Come on, Trace.
告诉我实话
Tell the truth.
好吧 安迪 你对那家伙知道些什么
All right, Andy. Tell us everything you know about this guy.
不是很多
I mean, not much.
韦伯是8个月前突然冒出来的
Webber shows up one day, like, eight months ago…
而且装的像是我最好的朋友 他很奇怪 太过于做作了
acting like he's my best friend. Kind of weird, like trying too hard.
他一定知道你们是双胞胎
He must have known you guys are twins.
他为什么要改名字？为什么不说出真相？
Why change his name? Why not just tell the truth?
不知道
No idea.
萨姆？
Sam?
萨姆？萨姆
Sam. Sam.
萨姆？
Sam!
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
我常带我的女人来这
I take my ladies here.
她们都喜欢这里
They like it.
我是说 因为我喜欢 所以 她们当然也喜欢了
Well, I mean, I like it, so of course they do too.
求你了 让我回家吧
Please. I just wanna go home.
别哭
Stop crying.
嘿
Hey.
我知道了 我知道你看上安迪的什么了
I get it. I see what you see in Andy.
他是个天才 那些他读的书…
I mean, he's a genius. Books he reads?
他将来一定出人头地
He's gonna be a great man someday.
但是他是我的家人 不是你的
But he is my family, not yours.
你不能拥有他
You can't have him.
今晚之后 你就不会了
You're not gonna have anything after tonight.
- 迪恩 你不用过去 - 没问题
- Dean, you should stay back. - No argument here.
我已经被控制的够呛了
I've had my head screwed with enough for one day.
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
- 安迪… - 特蕾西就在那啊
- Andy, no. - If it's Tracy out there…
我要去
then I'm coming.
好了 嘘 嘘 慢慢来
Okay. Slower.
特蕾西… 认真地听我说 好吗？
Tracy, I want you to listen to me very carefully, okay?
当我们说完后…
When we're done here…
我要你走在那边大坝的沿上
I want you to head over to the edge of that dam.
好吗？
Okay?
好的
Okay.
你到了那后…
And when you get there…
想象着自己能飞翔
you're gonna think you can fly.
然后就从那儿跳下去
And you're just gonna step right off.
你… 你能飞 不是吗？
You can fly, can't you?
是的 我能
Yeah, I think so.
也许会点吓人 但我要你说没事的
You might get scared, but I want you to say that it's okay.
对自己说 「一切都很好」
Just tell yourself, "Everything is okay."
从车里滚出来 马上
Get out of the car. Now!
你不会想这么做的
You really don't wanna do this.
特雷斯 给我你的手 过来 过来
Tracy. Come here, come here. Andy! I can't.
我控制不了自己
I couldn't control myself. It's all right.
嘿 别动 别动
Don't move. Don't move.
- 不要 不要 - 我要杀了你
- No, no. - I will kill you!
安迪 嘿 嘿 嘿 不 不 我来处理
Hey, let me handle this, all right? No.
我要杀了你
I'll kill him. I'll handle this.
安迪 听我说 听我说
I will kill you. Andy, listen to me. Listen to me
特蕾西 住手
Tracy, stop.
我说了 住手
I said, stop it.
- 你怎么做到的？- 多练习 兄弟
- How did you do that? - Practice, bro.
如果你练过 就会知道
If you'd just practice, you would know.
有时… 不需要用说的
Sometimes, you don't need to use your words.
必要的时候 可以全靠这里
If you have to, all you need is this.
- 有时会有点头痛 但值得 - 你个变态的混蛋
- Sometimes the headache's worth it. - You son of a bitch.
退后 安迪 不然特蕾西就要飞了
Back off, Andy, or Tracy's gonna do a little flying.
是吧 特雷斯？
Aren't you, Trace?
我比你强 我能做到
I'm stronger than you. I can do it.
好吧 好吧 好吧
Okay, okay. Okay.
好吧 只要… 不伤害她
All right, just please don't hurt her.
别对我生气 好吗？我知道 这是不对的
Don't be mad at me, okay? I know, it's all wrong.
我不是有意的 只是…
I didn't mean for this to happen. It's just…
特蕾西… 她想破坏我们
Tracy, she's trying to come between us.
- 你疯了 - 她是垃圾 伙计 他们都是
- You're insane. - She's garbage. Man, they all are.
我们能控制他们 做我们想要他们做的事
We can push them. We can make them do whatever we want.
你真的… 你真的这么蠢吗？这是…
Are you really this stupid? Is it?
当你知道有孪生兄弟时 你可以打电话给他
You learn you got a twin, you call him up.
约他喝杯东西 不用杀人啊
You go out for a drink. You don't start killing people.
我很早就想告诉你了 兄弟
I wanted to tell you for so long, bro.
但是… 他不让我说 他说我得等到时机成熟…
But he didn't let me. He said I had to wait until the time
- 谁？- 一个黄眼睛的男人
- Who? - The man with the yellow eyes.
你在说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
他来找我… 在我梦里
He came to me, in my dream.
他说我很特别
He said I was special.
告诉我他为我准备了一个很大的计划
He told me he's got big plans for me.
你还没明白吗 安迪 那是为了我们两个人好的
Wait till you see what's in store, Andy, for both of us.
是他告诉我有个兄弟
See, he's the one who told me that I had a brother.
一个孪生兄弟
A twin.
你为什么要杀了我们的妈妈？还有詹宁斯医生？
Why did you kill our mother? And why Dr. Jennings?
因为他们拆散了我们
Because they split us up!
他们毁了我们的生活 安迪
They ruined our lives, Andy.
我们早就该在一起了
We could have been together this whole time.
而不是独自生活
Instead of alone.
我不会让他们得逞的
I couldn't let them do that.
不会让他们逍遥的 不
I couldn't let them get away with that. No.
我看见你了
I see you.
再见了
Bye bye.
他是饮弹自尽的
He shot himself.
你们都看到了
And you all saw it happen.
是的
Yeah. We did.
看看他 他越来越得心应手了
Look at him. He's getting better at it.
你会没事的 小姐
You'll be okay, miss.
她看都不看我一眼
Won't even look at me.
是的 她被吓坏了
Yeah, she's pretty shaken up.
不 这… 这不一样 这是…
No, it's This is different. This is, uh…
我之前从没在她身上用过我的能力 在昨晚以前
I never used my mind thing on her before last night.
她现在害怕我了
She's scared of me now.
安迪 我讨厌这么做 但是 恩… 我们得离开这里了
Andy, I hate to do this, but, um, we have to get out of here.
这里 我写下了我的手机号
Here. I wrote down my cell.
你不是孤独一人的 好吗？
You don't have to be alone in this.
如果有事发生 就打给我
If anything comes up, you call me up.
那… 什么
Wha…? What…?
- 那我现在该怎么做？- 做个好人 安迪…
- What am I supposed to do now? - You be good, Andy.
否则我们就会回来
Or we'll be back.
看起来我是对的
Looks like I was right.
- 关于什么？- 安迪
- About what? - Andy.
到头来他还是个杀手
He's a killer after all.
不 他是英雄 他救了他女朋友和我的命
No, he's a hero. He saved his girlfriend, he saved my life.
但起码 昨晚他杀了人
Bottom line, last night, he wasted somebody.
是的 但是他不是个口吐白沫的神经病
He's not a foaming at the mouth psycho.
他只是… 被逼那样做的
He was just He was pushed into that.
从他的角度看 韦伯也是被逼的
Webber was pushed, in his own way.
马克斯 米勒也是 该死 我也是被杰西卡的死所逼的
Max Miller was pushed. I was pushed by Jessica's death.
你想说什么 萨姆？
What's your point?
只要环境合适 每个人都会杀人… 每个人
Right circumstances, everyone's capable of murder.
也许这就是那个魔鬼在做的 逼迫我们
Maybe that's what the demon's doing, pushing us
想方设法地摧垮我们
finding ways to break us.
我们还不知道他的目的 好吗？
We don't know what the demon wants, okay?
别担心了
Quit worrying about it.
之前我听到你说的了 迪恩 当安迪让你说出真相的时候
I heard you before, Dean, when Andy made you tell the truth.
- 你和我一样害怕这样事发生 - 我是被控制了心智
- You're just as scared of this as I am. - That was mind control.
就像是被灌了迷药 那不算数的
It's like being roofied, man. It doesn't count.
- 什么 - 不 我 我要重来
- What? - No, I'm calling do over.
- 你是7岁小孩吗？- 有什么关系
- Are you 7? - Doesn't matter.
我们只要继续做我们该做的就行了
We gotta keep doing what we're doing
找到那个邪恶的杂种 然后杀了他
find that evil son of a bitch and kill it.
是的 我想也是
Yeah. I guess.
你好？
Hello?
埃伦 怎么了？
Ellen, what's going on?
是的 我们就到
Yeah, we'll be right there.
乔？去拿一箱啤酒来
Jo, go pull up another case of beer.
- 妈… - 马上 行吗？
- Mom - Now. Please.
那么 你们 呃 你们想要说说这次猎杀的东西吗？
So you, uh, wanna tell me about this last hunt of yours?
- 不想 - 真的不了
- No - not really.
无意冒犯 这只是件家事
No offense. It's just kind of a family thing.
不再是了
Not anymore.
我从阿什那拿到的
I got this stuff from Ash.
安得烈·加拉赫的房子 在他6个月大时被烧的
Andrew's house burned down on his 6 month birthday…
和你们家一样
just like your house.
你们觉得这也是那个魔鬼做的 是吧？
You think it was the demon both times.
他也盯上加拉赫家了？
It went after Gallagher's family?
- 是的 我们觉得是的 - 萨姆
- Yeah, we think so. - Sam.
- 为什么？- 不关你的事
- Why? - None of your business.
对我说话注意点 小子
You mind your tongue with me, boy.
者不只是你们的战斗 是所有人的
This isn't just your war, this is war.
有件恐怖的大事就要发生了
Something big and bad is coming, and fast.
而且来的很快 也看不清对方的底细 现在我们至少要…
Their side holds all the cards. Now, at best, all we got is us.
团结起来 不要再半遮半掩的了
Together. No secrets or half truths here.
在外面有一些人
There are people out there.
像安迪 加拉赫…
Like Andy Gallagher.
像我一样的…
Like me.
还有 嗯… 我们都有某种能力
And we all have some kind of ability.
- 能力？- 是的 超能力
- Ability? - Yeah. Psychic ability.
我的话 我能 嗯… 我能看见影像…
Me, I have, um, visions.
前兆 我不知道 和别人的都不一样
Premonitions. I don't know, it's different for everybody.
那个魔鬼说过 他为我们这样的人准备了一个计划
The demon said he had plans for people like us.
- 什么计划？- 我们还不能肯定
- What kind of plans? - We don't know for sure.
那些人 那些有超能力的人 他们危险吗？
These people out there, these psychics. They dangerous?
不 不是全部
No. Not all of them.
但有些人是 有些人非常危险
But some are. Some are very dangerous.
- 有多少？- 还没有找到确切的数字
- How many of them we looking at? - We've been able to track a pattern.
在他们6个月大时 他们的房子都起过大火
They had house fires the night of the kid's 6 month birthday.
- 不是的 - 什么？
- That's not true. - What?
韦伯或者叫安塞姆·威姆斯 不管他叫什么…
Webber, or Anson Weems, or whatever his name is.
我看过他的档案 没有发生过火灾
I looked at his files, and there was no house fire.
没有不正常的
There's nothing out of the ordinary.
那就没有规律了
Which breaks pattern.
那么如果有其他像他那样的人 那就不在那个范围内
If there's others like him, there'd be nothing in the system.
就没有办法追踪到他们
No way to track them all down.
那么谁会知道外面有多少这样的人？
So who knows how many of them are really out there?
- 乔 亲爱的？- 什么事？
- Jo, honey. - Yeah?
最好去开瓶威士忌吧
Better break out the whiskey instead.